Lionel Messi: Destiny is a documentary film directed by Alexander Hill.
Behind-the-scenes documentary about how Lionel Messi succeeded in lifting the World
Cup – the only trophy to have eluded him in an incredible career.
Self, played by Lionel Messi.
Self, played by Lionel Scaloni.
Self, played by Emiliano Martínez.
Self, played by Alexis Mac Allister.
Self, played by Julián Álvarez.
Self, played by Gary Lineker.
The 76th annual Cannes Film Festival took place from 16 to 27 May 2023.
Swedish filmmaker Ruben Östlund served as jury president.
With the French film Anatomy of a Fall winning the Palme d'Or, the festival's top prize, Justine Triet became the
third female director to achieve the prize, after Jane Campion in 1993, and Julia Ducournau in 2021.
The official poster for the festival featuring actress Catherine Deneuve was created by Lionel Avignon and Stefan de Vivies of
the design studio Hartland Villa from a photo taken by Jack Garofalo during the shooting of La Chamade (1968).
The poster was chosen to pay tribute to Deneuve for her contributions to film.
During the festival, two Honorary Palme d'Or were awarded: the first one during the opening ceremony for Michael Douglas, and the second
one was awarded on short notice for Harrison Ford before the world premiere of Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny.
The festival opened with Jeanne du Barry by Maïwenn and
closed with Pixar's Elemental by Peter Sohn.